Sitting down at the NFL annual meeting
with owner Carrie Walton Penner. Carrie,
we are about 2 months removed from an
AFC Championship game appearance. A lot
of exciting initiatives coming up. How
would you characterize the momentum of
the organization heading into 2026? The
momentum is really exciting. Not only
for the Broncos, but for our fans across
Broncos country. Our players are coming
back in a few short weeks. Off the
field, it's amazing to watch the
momentum grow as we get ready to move
into our new training facility.
And uh we'll be doing that in just a
couple of months. And then, you know,
looking at and thinking about a new
stadium. And a lot of the work with
neighborhood organizations and city
council members, the mayor, really all
of our partners in thinking about and
looking at our preferred site in Burnham
Yard and getting ready for uh you know,
that momentum to continue. Absolutely.
Uh speaking about moving across the
field in just a few months to the new
Broncos Park powered by Common Spirit.
What's it been like to see the progress
there? And what do you think the biggest
benefit for the organization is in
moving into the new training center?
Well, it's been exciting to watch it
across the field um as it has, you know,
from groundbreaking until uh to today.
And so, uh we're just now getting ready
to put some final touches on over the
next couple months and then get ready to
move across.
You know, a couple of things in terms of
the great benefit that this will bring.
Part of it is we're staying in our home
and we're just moving across field. So,
um so I think that the energy that comes
with that is fantastic. We as an
organization, we will be bringing most
of the folks from the stadium who work
up there into the building. And so,
having the organization all together
will make a huge difference in terms of
having one organization, one team that
really are um all together and located
um in our new facility.
And then for players, it really is all
about the players. And from ground zero,
first floor, it is the players floor.
And they have the heart of that is their
locker room. It's a much uh bigger and
enhanced locker room. But all around
them, we we designed it with the idea
that we want our players taking as few
steps as possible to get everything that
they need and have access to everything
they need. And uh really conserve their
energy for getting things done on the
field.
As we continue to move toward Burnham
Yard as the preferred site for a new
stadium, how vital has the local
community feedback been to the start of
this process? Yeah, well, it's been
fantastic and it's been really exciting.
Part of it's been really exciting to
hear and learn about the history of
Burnham Yard. But we're still in
listening mode right now, doing a lot of
work with um community members, um city
council, the mayor's office. The
governor's been very a great partner and
very supportive. The momentum is
certainly there and and we're excited to
partner across the community um to make
this an incredible year-round
opportunity for Denver and for the
organization. Carrie, obviously the
Broncos are not alone in this stadium
project. A lot of other stakeholders.
Can you tell me a little bit more about
what this process is like with all of
those stakeholders in the community?
Yes. Well, so we have a number of
different processes in place and and
kind of running simultaneously to each
other. We really are getting to a point
where we're um all of these partnerships
and the conversations we and we need to
just keep making the timelines. But
it'll be an incredible project and it's
been a great thing to work on. Great to
partner with so many different
organizations and city council and other
offices across across the city and the
state. You know, it takes all of us. And
Damani and Tim have been doing an
amazing job for for us in being out
there and really listening to community
members and organizations and and
driving this forward. But the timeline
is aggressive and so we're we're looking
forward to getting a little bit uh
little bit more momentum there, too. We
just passed the 1-year anniversary of
the all-in-all covered unprecedented
initiative. We just aired a 9 News
special on Saturday. As you look back on
the past year and the impact of the
program, what makes you most proud? 99%
of high schools across Colorado and
programs have signed on to this. We have
distributed almost 4,000 helmets over
the last year. So, that's been really
exciting. Um and just to see that that
this is something that's creating
incredible momentum across Colorado is
fantastic. Absolutely. I know you're
involved in several different
committees. What does this week down
here at the annual meeting look like for
you? For the last few years, I've been
on the NFL Foundation board. And then um
the diversity committee. So, I've been
doing those for a few years. And this
year I added the player health and
safety.
All three of those really are in
alignment with what my background is and
and my engagement with the team as well
in different areas. So, you know, so
it's great to see a lot of the different
improvements, some of the rules that we
will be listening to tomorrow, the rule
recommendations and changes for players
on the field. And you know, as the NFL
continues to really focus on how do we
strengthen the game and how do we make
sure the game is as safe as possible,
it's exciting to be a part of that.
Absolutely. Well, Carrie, we appreciate
you spending some time with us. Thank
you and
Great. Thank you. Great to be here.